adzerk.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy

If you would like information on our privacy policy concerning data collection and usage as part of the [ad server](https://adzerk.com/blog/ad-server/) platform it provides to its customers, please read [Privacy Policy (Ad Serving)](https://dev.adzerk.com/v1.0/docs/privacy-policy-ad-server). 

Our core believes regarding user privacy and data protection are:

  * User privacy and data protection are human rights
  * We have a duty of care to the people within our data
  * Data is a liability, it should only be collected and processed when absolutely necessary
  * We will never sell, rent, or distribute your personal information

Adzerk, Inc (Adzerk) is committed to respecting the privacy of all persons using the adzerk.com website (the Site). This Privacy Policy describes Adzerk’s information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site and for administrative users of Adzerk’s services. It does not apply to information collected by Adzerk off-line or to information collected by licensees or users of Adzerk’s services, or to advertising networks with whom our users may connect. We encourage you to visit the Network Advertising Initiative ([http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)) for more information about online advertising networks and their privacy policies.

Every individual has the right to request what info (if any) we have on them, as well as request that we edit, delete, or transfer it. Adzerk honors all data rights, and if you'd like to delete any data we have, please reach out to support@adzerk.com.

**Web Forms and Adzerk Accounts**

When you establish your Adzerk account, purchase other services through our Site, or fill out a web form (such as "Contact Us"), you may provide us with your personal information, such as your name and email address.

We do not distribute or sell this information, although Adzerk does store this information with various third party data processors (see section below).

**Payments**

If you are set up to pay by credit card, then Adzerk or its payment processor will collect personally identifiable information (credit card number, billing address, phone number) and keep this information on file in our server in order to process your recurring invoices. This information is only used to verify credit card authenticity, and issue invoices as per your agreement with Adzerk. Upon discontinuation of your service, your credit card information will be deleted. If we are unable to process your subscription, this information, along with your account information, may be used to contact you.

**Site Visitation**

Like most websites, Adzerk.com uses Google Analytics to track user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages.

Although GA records data such as your location, device, internet browser, and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer's IP address, but Google does not grant us access to this. We consider Google to be a third party data processor (see below).

Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this site.

**Email Newsletters**

If you choose to join our email newsletter, the email address that you submit to us will be forwarded to [Mailchimp](https://www.mailchimp.com/), who provide us with email marketing services. We consider MailChimp to be a third party data processor (see below). Your e-mail will remain within this database for as long as we continue to use MailChimp's services for email marketing or until you request removal. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any email that we send you or by requesting removal via marketing@adzerk.com.

**Cookies**

Adzerk's marketing site does not drop cookies, except for Google Analytic's tracking cookie, which Adzerk has no visibility into. Please see the third-party section below for more information on GA.

Adzerk will use the personal information you provide to provide requested services, alert you of new products and services, features and enhancements, respond to your support issues, and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, promotions, and special offers. You agree that we may communicate with you via email and any similar technology for any purpose relating to the Site.

We may also:

Disclose your personal information to companies who work for Adzerk to provide a product or service to you that you have requested or to process payments. Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.  
Release personal information and/or other information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state, federal or international laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other government request.  
Disclose personal information and/or other information about you that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our agreements, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Site, and protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Adzerk, our users or others.

Adzerk does not knowingly allow children under the age of eighteen (18) to sign up for an account on the Site or to otherwise disclose any of their personal information to us. If you are under 18 years old, please do not use or access our Site. We do not intend to collect information about children under the age of 18. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 18 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s information from our systems. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 whom you believe has disclosed personal information to us, please contact us at support@adzerk.com so that we may delete and remove the child’s information from our systems.

We provide you the opportunity to opt out of receiving certain communications from us and our business partners, at the point in the registration process where we request information about you. In addition, all marketing e-mails from Adzerk will provide you with the opportunity to unsubscribe from future marketing mailings. Even if you opt out of such mailings, however, we reserve the right to send you e-mail and other communications to disclose maintenance and other service-related issues.

Please contact us at support@adzerk.com if you need to update and/or correct your account information. Alternately, if you are a registered user of Adzerk’s service, you can change your account information through the management component of the service. You may need to supply certain information so that we can try to verify that you have authority to modify this information.

The Site may contain links to other Internet sites. We have no responsibility for the privacy practices of other websites, including the websites of our business partners. Whenever a web browser window is opened in Adzerk that does not show a web page created by Adzerk (noted by a Adzerk copyright statement at the bottom of such pages), then it should be assumed that Adzerk privacy policies do not apply.

We use a number of third parties to process personal data on our behalf. These third parties have been carefully chosen in respect to their privacy policies. These partners do not distribute or sell your information, and are used only for customer relationship purposes.

  * Email Storage: MailChimp, Formstack
  * CRMs: Intercom, Segment.io, Zendesk, Pipedrive
  * Tracking: Google Analytics

For a full list of sub-processors Adzerk uses, please visit [this page](https://dev.adzerk.com/v1.0/docs/sub-processors).

For Google Analytics, we collect anonymized data to track aggregated site visitor metrics and understand from where users are coming. Adzerk at no point has access to any PII or individual user data. Adzerk also uses GA for retargeting, which involves dropping a cookie that only Google can see. Because of the GDPR, Adzerk does retargeting just in the US. If you'd like to opt-out of Google's tracking, you can visit [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

We intend to protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible as described in this policy while also fulfilling our responsibility to uphold all applicable laws and regulations. Due to potential legal requirements and other possible circumstances, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed or accessed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. We may be compelled under law to disclose information to government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose any information to law enforcement or other government officials that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in compliance with the law.

In the event that all or part of Adzerk is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, you agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

We have implemented reasonable security measures on the Site to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. Additionally, Adzerk takes reasonable steps to ensure that our third party business partners, including our hosting partners, provide sufficient protection for personal information.

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically by Adzerk, as reflected by the “last modified” date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Material amendments to this Privacy Policy shall be communicated to you at the time you log into the Site, by e-mail, or by notice here. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the information handling practices of the Site, you may contact us at support AT adzerk.com.

Adzerk's DPA is aimed to help you feel confident that you are working with a GDPR-compliant partner and to save both parties from legal harm should the other party breach the agreement. The details of the DPA [live here](https://dev.adzerk.com/v1.0/docs/adzerk-data-processing-agreement).

Last Modified: April 10, 2018

Updated 9 months ago
